(Raj:)I'll get to celebrate
Diwali twice--
(Raj:)one at each house.
(Raj:)That's double the Diwali.
(Howard:)You sure you're okay?
(Raj:)I'm okay.
(Howard:)You don't look okay.
(wails): How can I be okay?
I come from a broken home.
(Leonard:)The doctor said I should be
out of surgery by 10:00.
(Amy:)Okay.
(Penny:)And Sheldon really believes
we're at a public swimming pool?
(Leonard:)He was so busy figuring out
how many parts per million
(Leonard:)of urine we'd be floating around
in, he didn't even question it.
(Sheldon:)18 parts per million.
(Sheldon:)And he's still doing it.
(Amy:)Don't worry about that.
I'm happy to take you to work.
(Sheldon:)Well, thank you.
(Sheldon:)And Leonard never lets me have
French toast sticks in the car.
(Sheldon:)I can't have syrupy fingers,
(Sheldon:)but he can do the backstroke
in a toilet bowl.
(Amy:)It's nice they're
getting exercise.
(Sheldon:)Although now that
I think about it,